Hello everyone.
I am Miyuki Handa, aka Miruten of Combined Curl Me.
Today I would like to ask Miyuki Handa 100 questions.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Miyuki Handa.
I was born on February 27, 2004, in a regional area.
My family consists of a father, a mother, an elder sister, and a younger brother.
I used to be a hamster girl. The origin of my name is Miyuki, like I want the fruit of Miyuki to become more and more polished and beautiful like a pearl.
There are many more, but they don't come up now.
I would like to ask my mom again.
My charm point is that I have long fingers, and when I told you that my nails are beautifully shaped, you complimented me on my gel nails.
My special skills are spinning and making frogs in an instant.
I can make a frog in an instant.
The songs I often sing at karaoke are "Koi ni kanaka" and "Chance" by Kirarin Devolution.
I am embarrassed to imitate what I can do.
Then I'll hide this one and do it.
When I was shopping, I met Pepper-kun, and he wrote something on a piece of paper, and I thought I could imitate him, and then I could do something.
What are your strengths?
It may be obvious, but I am punctual and always keep my promises.
What are your weaknesses?
I worry too much.
What is your motto?
The more fruitful the ears of rice are, the more they droop. I think this is very important.
I think this is very important.
I have it engraved in my heart. What nicknames have you been given outside of Biltine? It's embarrassing. Mii. Mii. I was called something like Mickey. It's a little embarrassing. Everyone calls me Biltine.
What did you want to be when you were a child? I wanted to be an idol. If I had to describe myself with one Chinese character, it would be "Pearl. This is also my name, which I love, and I love shiny pearls.
I want to be a sparkling person!
What is your favorite drink?
Water and Frappuccino.
Favorite sweets?
Ice cream, parfaits, pancakes, and pastard.
What is your favorite sushi dish?
Seared cheese salmon.
I ate three plates the other day.
That's all I ate.
What is your favorite ramen flavor?
To be honest, I can't really eat ramen,
But when I went to a ramen restaurant
Miso ramen.
I ordered something that even people who don't like ramen can eat.
Well, my favorite Sanrio character is Krami-chan and Han-Yu-Don.
What would you compare yourself to if you were an animal? I was asked this question in elementary school.
I answered, "A lizard." I don't know why.
What is your favorite season? Winter. Christmas, New Year's and my birthday.
I also like Valentine's Day because I can eat a lot of chocolate.
Who is your favorite person?
A gentle book that praises Moku Moku-chan's daily life.
I decided to read a page before painting, and I'm only halfway through.
I highly recommend it!
My favorite movie is a movie I saw during summer vacation in elementary school called "Meloette's Glittering Lysytll".
It's a movie with really cute characters.
My favorite anime is Yumeiro Patissier.
My favorite TV show is News Every.
It's always on at home when I come home from school.
It's because the special section is very heartwarming.
I often watch a youtube channel called "Noga Channel", where a guy says you can do sit-ups in 2 minutes.
My favorite comedian is A-BOSS.
My favorite idols are Gorabu, Niaju and AKB48!
Do you eat rice in the morning? Bread?
I like rice in the morning.
Do you wear pajamas to bed? Or hair shirt?
Pajamas! Fluffy pajamas help me sleep easily.
Indian? Outdoor?
Indian.
Rough in front
I'm rough with myself.
I'm not rough when it comes to people.
Dexterous? Clumsy?
Depends on the thing, but I like detailed work, so I might be dexterous.
What makes you happy?
Cute, pretty, pretty.
Cool! Cute by far! That's what I like.
I'm happy no matter how many times I hear the word "cute".
How do you spend your days off?
I have two patterns.
I make a day when I never leave the house.
I like to sleep in a dark room with no light coming in.
I also like to hang out with friends and go shopping.
It varies a lot.
How much sleep do you get on average?
It depends on the day, but usually 7 or 8 hours, sometimes 5 hours.It depends on the day, but usually 7 or 8 hours, sometimes 5.
I'm a bit of a compulsive person, and as you can see, my hands move very quickly. The driving force for me to live is when people tell me how cute I am and how much they love me.
What do you enjoy doing the most? Live performances and storytelling, of course.
But when I was working with the members on a trampoline project, we laughed so much because trampolines are so much fun.
I have a lot of fun when I'm playing Tramplin'.
How do you motivate yourself? Before I go to work, I say this before I leave the house. A straight face. When I'm sad, what do I look like? When I'm sad, I make a serious face. I make a face when I'm hungry? I make a face so big that my eyebrows stick together.
What's the funniest thing you've laughed about lately? I don't know if you'll find this funny... but when I was talking to Hirellin about crowded trains...
We were talking about what to do on a crowded train.
I mean, it's impossible, but if there's a certain number of people on the train...
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That person...
A-ha-ha-ha!
A-ha-ha-ha
ah-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's not funny.
They're putting people up on top.
But I like it that way.
Have you cried recently?
I cried because I had real muscle pain.
I cry easily when I have pain.
I found myself crying while going down the stairs.
Where do you want to travel the most?
I have never been to Hokkaido.
How do you release stress?
Talk, eat, sleep, and forget.
What do you like? Great politeness.
What are your fashion brands?
Ankerlage and Emmy A.N.K.
I have always admired and loved their clothes.
What's your hair style obsession?
It's a real mess.
To be honest, today's half-twin is not 100 points.
The amount, position, and height of the half-twins done by the dressmaker.
If these three conditions don't match up nicely, it's not a 100 points.
The diagonal line between the half-twin and the eye position is very important.
So today, it's a point to look a little fake.
I can't do it myself.
What is your fashion obsession?
Lots of frills and sparkles.
Ribbons.
What shampoo do you recommend?
I buy shampoo from a hair salon because I bleach my hair.
What is your favorite thing about Tachigi?
I can't talk about this enough.
I'm going to ask you to make a separate video.
When I go to the supermarket, there are so many gyoza (Chinese dumplings).
I love gyoza.
There's a huge area in the lueto corner just for dumplings.
There is a big area in the Lueto corner just for gyoza dumplings.
There are also many places for strawberry picking.
Let's go to Tachigi next time on the Enjoy Channel!
Which countries have you been to?
Hustan.
I ate a big salmon!
Where do you want to live in the future?
I've always wanted to be an architect.
I would like to build a very big house.
If you could be born again, what would you be?
I would like to be myself.
I'm really enjoying my life now, so I'd like to live it again.
What would you do if you had 300 million yen?
First of all, I would give 100 million yen to my family.
I'd save it up and buy some gold coins.
Maybe I should buy some gold coins or something.
If you could build a machine, what would you want to do?
I want to see what the future will be like.
I want to go to the future.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
A tent.
I would stay in the tent all the time.
I would hide in the tent all the time and not see any insects or animals.
What's the one tool you'd like to have from Doraemon?
A door that goes anywhere.
What would you like to do when you become human?
I'd like an eyelash perm shop.
When I close my eyes, what position do you use to do my eyelashes?
I'd like to know what position I'm in when I'm closing my eyes.
or "What do I look like when I do this with my lashes?
I'd be curious to know!I'm just curious.
What do you want to do when you become a man?
I don't know.
I'd like to be a man in Yoneda-hara.
What would you like to do once in your life?
I want to be in the graduation album.
There's a page that says "Person of the Year".
I want to be in it.
What is your dream for the future?
I want to be a person who can do anything.
Like doing the laundry every day.
I want to do the laundry and clean the house every day.
I want to be a motivated person.
What is the most attractive male gesture?
I wonder...
I don't know if it's a male or female thing, but...
But if it's thoughtful, isn't that good?
It grabs you.
Doing something for someone else
It's a very nice thing to do.
What's your favorite male hairstyle?
It's embarrassing.
But if you're really honest about it.
I think anything goes.
What is your favorite hairstyle for a woman?
Any hairstyle I want.
If it's what I want my hair to look like.
I think it's cute!
What emoji do you use most often?
I love hamsters.
I use hamsters.
What is your favorite line stamp?
I like the Kuromi emoji and the baby hamster stamp.
and a baby hamster stamp.
What do you think your previous life was like?
I did a past life test online once.
It came up as a man who wrote poems in the Heian period (794-1192).
What's the cutest thing you can think of to say?
The prettiest thing in this room.
I'll go with this one.
Cushion.
Yes, sir.
Say the most handsome word you can think of.
What? What's that?
Like ass? I don't know.
Forgive me for saying it like that.
Say the hardest word you can think of.
Shidoro-gyo
Who is your best friend among your collaborators and who would you like to be friends with?
I would like to be friends with Chiara Taito.
When I met her the other day
When I met her the other day, she asked me to have dinner with her next time.
I was so happy!
I am looking forward to that day.
Who is your good friend and who would you like to be good friends with?
Julie.
She took me under her wing because I was very shy.
She talked to me and was fun to talk to.
Which member did you think was noisy?
As Mirei said.
All of them.
Everyone was really noisy.
Of course, they can be quiet.
Which member do you think is cute?
All of them.
Oh, Nanka took a picture.
Who do you think is the best? When she asks me "Who do you think is the best?
She has a cute way of saying it, doesn't she?
I'm the only one who knows how cute Nanka-chan is.
What's the moment when you feel attracted to a member?
When we hold hands with the other members.
And when Mirei put her hand in the space between my arms
And when Mirei put her hand in between my arms and hugged me...
I was like, "Yay, I don't have to go and join hands with them.
I felt like I didn't have to go and join hands with them.
What is your favorite Not Equal Me song?
When a tree falls in the middle of an empty forest, does it make a sound?
What is your favorite Not Equal Me lyric?
Not Equal Me's "The story that was meant to begin with you
That's the word...I'm really attached to that word.
I'm really attached to it.
I'm going to love this lyric for a long time to come.
I love all the lyrics.
What is your favorite outfit for Not Equal Me?
I love the Mirenani outfit.
And 24 Girls' sparkly outfit?
I love it, it looks like a gaffe princess!
What is your favorite Not Equal Me dance?
My accent.
It's very difficult.
It's very difficult, but I think it would be great if I could dance it well.
What is your most memorable live concert?
Noemi's first concert.
It was my first concert and I was so nervous.
It was the first time for me to see my fans in a long time.
I felt a lot of emotions.
It was the concert that made me want to work harder as an idol from now on.
If you could go to karaoke with the members alone, who would it be?
Who would you go with?
Momo.
Just listening to Momo's songs.
I want to spend that kind of time.
Who would you go to Yakiniku with?
Who would you go with?
I would go with Carin.
Because she seems to be good at grilling meat.
If you were to go to Hawaii with a member, who would it be?
Who would you go with?
Uh...
Saya.
Saya, you were in Passion when you were at Histo.
You were talking to the staff at the restaurant.
I thought that was great.
I'd like to bring that strong feeling with me.
Which member would you like to switch with?
Nacchan.
I love your positive attitude and happy way of thinking.
I really love your positive attitude and happy way of thinking.
I really want to be Nacchan.
Which member would you like to be combined with?
Ehh...
I want to be Meiko.
Meiko has really long arms and legs.
I think they would be really long if they were combined.
The "Heavenly God's Majesty" program has been decided by the above-mentioned groups.
What kind of program?
Mystery of the World Miruten
I'll get lots of little me-too's!
Speaking of which, what did you eat this morning?
I ate a piece of chocolate.
I'm starving.
What do you want to eat after this recording is over?
What do you mean by "sweet"?
I want to eat sushi for the rest of my life.
Do you prefer dogs or cats?
If I had to keep a dog, I would keep a dog.
But I want a cat to be near me.
Are you a mushroom mountain person? Taketokonosato?
I am overwhelmingly in favor of takenokonosato.
What is the punishment game you want to play in a variety show?
I've been saying this for a long time.
I would like to receive the cream method.
There are many theories.
It's not too sweet.
I like cream, so I think it's okay.
What kind of punishment do you not want to do on a variety show?
There are too many.
But I really want to be allowed to eat bugs.
What do you want to do for the 200,000th anniversary of Ikonaijyoi channel?
I like to watch night routine.
I like to watch them.
I would like to see the routines of the members.
What is your goal for this year?
It's my last routine.
I want to be 19 years old with no regrets
And to be 20 years old
I want to turn 20 without any worries.
Any last words to your fans?
Thank you all for liking me
but thank you for liking me.Thank you for thinking I liked it.
I thought I wanted to ask you 100 questions again.
It was fun.
I look forward to working with you again in the future.
That's all.